<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on irfys digital garden</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on irfys digital garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Flat Place</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book/books_a_flat_place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book/books_a_flat_place/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Read in July 2024. Storygraph link &#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.thestorygraph.com/books/307300fe-ebb8-481f-9652-4a2b1dc284e0&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and written by Noreen Masud. I got this as part of the non-fiction book subscription from &#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://libreria.io/&#34;&gt;Libreria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Summary&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#summary&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many things that I could say about this book, many of them perhaps not suitable to be published to the internet. I don&amp;rsquo;t really how to feel after reading this, but this is the only recent book in memory that has stirred up such strong emotions, and resonant emotions that I recognise intimately.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book/books_summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book/books_summary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to summarise briefly interesting books that I&amp;rsquo;ve read to refer to later or just to reflect on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Range, Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Breath - The New Science of a Lost Art]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Superforecasting , The Art &amp;amp; Science of Prediction]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[A Flat Place]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breath - The New Science of a Lost Art</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book/books_breath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book/books_breath/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Read over the summer of 2023, storygraph link &#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.thestorygraph.com/books/b4a34771-12f7-4e86-8244-1b90be91947f&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and written by James Nestor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The title is a bit more sensationalist than the contents, but the content I still found informative. The book is less of a manual for breathing techniques, and more of a personal reflection and journey by Nestor as to how he tried overcoming his health problems and satiated his curiosity using the art of breathing. The actual practical manual section is still included though, and is neatly summarised in the back of the book with a link to all the exercises online at &#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mrjamesnestor.com/breath&#34;&gt;his website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Range, Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book/books_range/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book/books_range/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some thoughts and lessons from the book &#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/41795733-range&#34;&gt;Range: Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World&lt;/a&gt;, which I read in January 2021. The writing style was very engaging - you can see clearly where Epstein&amp;rsquo;s sports writing experience has come in here, and was highly enjoyable to read. Each chapter laid out a strong, clear concept, backed up by either research, anecdotes, biographies, or similar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to note down the key takeaways from the book, for future reference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superforecasting , The Art &amp; Science of Prediction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/book/books_superforecasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/book/books_superforecasting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Read in winter of 2023, borrowed from the analytical library at work (made up of books kindly donated by team members!). The authors are Philip Tetlock and Dan Gardner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The entirety of the book is actually summarised pretty well in the &amp;lsquo;commandments&amp;rsquo; given at the end, which I&amp;rsquo;ve copied at the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall it follows a standard pop science layout, using anecdotes and compelling narrative to bring home clear points, and I think it does a good job doing so. It touches on case studies from news, economies, and intelligence agencies (which is what I found most interesting), and also talks about the authors own experiences running forecasting tournaments. There are apparently also forecasting markets out there, which I gather are similar to betting markets (albeit I guess with more &amp;lsquo;intellectulism&amp;rsquo;). Actually, that&amp;rsquo;s a good point - at what point do you classify forecasting as betting?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
